by H.
NOKIZAKA under construction
Boom! Here we go, NOKIZAKA Construction Work in progress!
I'm Bananaman, your host, and I look forward to working with you.
I'm Bananaman, your host.
Please come in.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well...
Ready?
Wow!
Oh, my God.
What a surprise!
Oh, I don't suppose you had it in your dressing room?
Yes, I did.
Sweets.
You didn't know? Catering.
Wasn't it in Mr. Himuro's dressing room?
What's going on?
Himuro-san is so tired of all this.
That's right.
He'd leave a gift like this and forget about it.
I'm usually very careful now.
I'm looking forward to going backstage later.
He's really like that.
So, today's project, Mr. Himuro, please.
The gimmick club.
It's actually a very important part of the variety show.
A gimmick who carries out missions behind the scenes.
This time, we'll be examining the gimmickry of the members on location.
It's not just for variety shows.
It's a job to be a gimmick.
If you can do this, you will get more work.
And those who are caught by the pure ones will also get more work.
This time, we will call the members to record a survey and interview for the show.
The gimmick person will set up various missions to the target.
The first mission is to set up a towel with four towels.
The first mission is to set up a buzzing cushion
Can you induce the members to sit on one of the four chairs?
The trick of the challenger is a chiribiri pen
Can you make him use one of the three pens prepared?
And finally, the last challenge is to make the target drink the noodle soup that is hidden in the catering.
I have to say I'm going to drink this.
There are three of them.
I'm so nervous!
I was so nervous.
Are you sitting down?
Did you sit down?
It's easy for me to say, "I'm sitting down.
That doesn't happen very often.
But this should put him on his guard.
He's leading Persimmon to the buzzing cushion with a pretentious face.
That's good!
He easily passed the first mission with a smile and a laugh!
What a surprise!
I thought that's why there are four cushions...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll take that one.
Oh, you already have them?
You're dragging a booboo cushion.
You guys.You guys.
I'm scared of Kamurai.
You're good.
That's good.
That's great.
I've already had the second one... and so have I.
It was chattering.
While the persimmon was fading on the booboo cushion.
While the persimmons were being decimated by the booboo cushion.
Tried the booboo cushion herself
Catching the persimmon even more off guard.
The result
It was a brilliant plan, and the mission was a success!
Was it true?
Bullshit.
Push it.
What the hell?
It hurts.
Are you going for the second one?
Tamura proceeds so far without any suspicion
The last men-tsuyu mission!
How do you do this?
Can I drink it?
I think so.
I'll have a Coke.
Have a Coke.
That's a pickup artist's word.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Here?
I haven't had a drink yet today.
That sounded like a Coke.
That's what it sounds like.
I don't know what's in there.
I wonder what this is.
Soy sauce?
I don't think so.
Japanese title.
Surika.
Oblivious to the oysters approaching from behind
The men-tsuyu is revealed
A painful mistake
You didn't.
Can we recover from this?
I'm sure.
Drink this.
And?
No, I can't.
No.
No, I'm just saying, maybe we're talking about the wrong thing.
Why not?
Well, we'll get him to drink it.
We'll get him to drink it.
Oh, it's concentrated.
It's a super power play.
It's so obvious.
The cough, it's like he's telling his allies
It was really good
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I didn't salt it enough.Yeah, yeah, yeah. I didn't salt it enough.
Just the right amount.
He said it again.
After all that food, he ended the meal with a natural "boo-boo"!
You can't even tell he's a chef now.
What do you think this place is?
What's this?
What do you think it is?
Play.
Tamura rolled the shaking persimmon in the palm of his hand
Mission accomplished!
The next trick was a tough one.
In addition to the booboo cushion and chattering pen
in addition to the booboo cushion chattering pen, he also stuck a piece of nori (seaweed) from his lunch box on his teeth so that he wouldn't be recognized and startled.
The tooth remission challenge!
It's hard to stick it on your teeth
The last one is hard
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Yay!
Secretary of Staff took the safe pen from the partially-played Semia River
He succeeded in getting the pen chattering in the blink of an eye!
I'm chattering away!
I don't have the strength to set this up.
Welcome back.
What are you two doing together?
Oh, it's gone! It fell right out!
Why did it fall?
Did it always happen?
Nothing.
What? You know?
I didn't tell you.
It's the next part of the pampering plan.
I tried to lead him on, but...
But the spiritual wind was a dud.
I decided to start writing an arcade for the time being.
Oops!
Wow!
Oh, this is so difficult!
Shizuki didn't even think of an error
Seimya automatically sat back down
Wow!
Lucky Boo-Boo!
It's not Ray.
Oh, I see.
Cute.
Cute. This is cute.
No, it's cute.
Cute.
I think Mr. Ray won.
Tension Boom is already moving on to the third mission!
What?
He said he's going to move it.
Mission.
Ah...
That's the hard part.
It's hard.
What? You didn't raise it.
Maybe you already have.
I have a groove.
I knew it!I knew it.
I wish I could stay beside you all the time
While Seimya is having a good time
I'm secretly approaching Kanori.
You're early!
It's too soon!
The most important thing
This is the only thing
I'm keeping it for Jason.
LOL!
Cute.
Where the canoli is brilliantly set.
The opposition is unbeatable.
I didn't feel like I'm in nature itself.
So you're saying I can set it up?
Oh, no.
You mean I can set it up?
That's funny.
We had a few lucky breaks along the way.
But he completed the mission with overwhelming speed!
Nice work.
Seimya and
I thought it was a little suspicious.
The chairs don't usually have mats like that.
on the top.
I thought maybe this thing was going to conduct an electric current.
I sat down with a bit of trepidation.
But there wasn't any.
And when I pull it, it goes "boo".
I see.
The next trickster is Kaki. He's going on a three-way mission against Kanagawa.
Kaki, both of them.
Kaki, is this after?
After it's done.
Okay, let's try this again.
Sit here.
I'll sit there.
Takumi?
Takumi.
I failed to get him to sit on the booboo cushion.
And I couldn't get him to sit on the booboo cushion. And I couldn't get him to sit on the pen either.
And while I was distracted by the lunch box, Kanagawa took the ordinary pen, too.
Is this going to be the first time I've failed in all of my attempts?
What is this?
Let's have some tea!
What?
What's this about judging?
One taste.
Is this seaweed?
You're early.
That was quick.
Please add a word to Anpanman and make it a nightmare.
How many?
Poison Bus Anpanman.
LOL!
LOL!LOL!
That's great.
I didn't do it on purpose.
You didn't know.
I knew it! It's because of the seaweed.
You're a genius.
Can I see it?
That seaweed is delicious!
As the leafy seaweed flowed, Kanagawa got up from his seat and went to the catering zone.
Here's where the persimmons move even more.
Can I see your face?
Yes, you can.
This is good.
Is it good?
What shall we do?
I want to make Anpanman look bad.
Poison gas anpanman.
Eww...
LOL!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha.
How do you do that with your hands?
How are you using your hands?
Time's up for the two of you here.
I guess I can't do the Bilibili Pen.
But you made up for your mistake in the first half
Two missions completed.
It's a good thing I wasn't dumbfounded.
Next, Samura, Katta, and Kanaga tried their hand at the next challenge!
Three people in a trap?
That's scary!
Endo wanted to get close to us so bad, he got beat up!
The three of us were on a mission to get the three of us to the next level.
Kanagawa stood by with a cardboard box over his head
to get close enough to scare the target so that he doesn't notice.
In addition, the team members were set up outside the door to hang out.
the first target out of the room.
I see.
It's not cardboard at all.
I'll sit in front of the soccer.
I'll sit right in front of the soccer.
Kaki's shoulder tackle leads Endo to the target seat at the beginning of the mission
I'll make him sit in the best position for the cardboard Kanagawa.
I won't lie.
I've calmed down too.
Lying in life is the best thing you can do
It's the best thing I've ever done.
I see. I'll come closer.
Can I have a drink, then?
Oh, shit.
Make me look bad.
You can make him look bad.
How much do you know about Anpanman?
I know a lot.
Yes, you do. You like persimmons.
Tamura leads the chion and attracts Endo.
and finish the cardboard and mentsue at the same time.I'm going to finish the cardboard and the menzue at the same time.
That's amazing.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought, "I love it.
It's so good.
It's great!
Here's a cardboard Kanagawa arriving right behind the endo!
You can even go this far.
When you cut too much bangs.
Everyone's high smash of the day!
Wow!
Wow.
You scared me.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
You scared the shit out of me.
What's up?
What's the matter?
It's a lime in Hokkaido.
It's like an undercover operation.
No, no, no.
Why? Why?
Why?
For some mysterious and obviously dubious reason.
Kanagawa joins
and started preparing for the next mission.
I want to go in the cardboard box too!
Don't go in there!
Let's go in, Sacchan!
I can't!
I can't go in there, either.
Come on, let's go in, too.
I'll try.
But you know what?
Kakito's pretty tall.
I...
I'd like to replace him with someone else.
Do it.
Doubtful.
How'd it go?
Give it a shot.
I can't see it now.
Oh, God.
I just had to force the end to stand up.
To replace the drinks.
What do you want me to say?
Oh, shit.
Tuning show.
Cute.
I'll put a top on it then.
What are you doing?
It's a good thing we switched them here.
Switching it out...
That's how we switched it.I switched it with that one.
Oh, it's cute.
So cute!
What are you doing?
He's so cute!
It's so cute!
I'll write it down.
So, what's the first lie?
The train was one stop late.
I'm back.
I've said that before.
I did.
That's a big one.
He's got his mouth full.
Poor little Sakku.
Poor little guy.
I won't drink it.
It hurts.
Tasty?
Oh, my God.
What is it?
It's thick.
Dark?
It's strong.
Why?
That's not a very strong reaction.
Why that reaction?
So, the last mission of this intense conversation
Can you lead them naturally to the fairy tale where the tub awaits?
I can't get him to come.
Go get him.
How did you do that?
It's dense.
It's amazing.
It's thick, isn't it?
It's me.
I don't mind.
You said it was the sound of your fingers.
Say it once.
You like me, don't you?
And when you force Endo to come to the door...
I'm scared.
You only like me, don't you, Sakura?
No, you don't.
You like me, don't you?
Cherry blossoms
I feel like I'm sinking.
It's something different, isn't it?
It's because...
You two are amazing!
That's right
It's the same as usual
As usual...As usual
As usual.
Is that a little out of place?
He drags the frightened Endo around from start to finish.
All missions completed.
Oh, my God.
We'll see how Tsutsui's tricks work from here on out.
Interesting
First of all, the balloon mission against Rika Sato
She cheated the sound with just her seat, and when she got the "luck line"...
Yay!
But when it comes to the movie version...
Wow!
That's right!
Surprise!
And the end doesn't bifork too?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What the hell? Why is it so scary?
And then there was the cardboard mission against Matsuno...
I approached him without any hesitation, standing on my knees, not caring about the noise...
Miyuki, you're going to notice, right?
Wow!
Surprise, that one.
I don't think anyone is here.
They don't notice this.
Just Rankin, who draws out Matsuno's reaction at the end of the messy trick...
What was it about the end that made everyone want to come closer together?
That's right!
The moment I came in, we all had so much momentum.
They were a bit of a bad bunch, weren't they?
I thought something might be wrong.
After that, the third term trickster, who's this?
Next, the third term student, Tokai, who went to Shikaku, tried two missions against Mezawa.
Please do me a favor.
I really want to take the time to fill out the questionnaire.
Are there so many different kinds of pens?
This one looks easy to write with.
This one's too thin.
What's that?
Umezawa was very wary of the suspicious pens right from the start.
But at least Sato was not suspected and the mission continued.
And Sato was wondering how men-tsuyu works.
What did you do with it?
Mission.
A double-bottle style piece where something else might happen apart from the mission
Looks like he's going to spill his weapon
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
Spill it, spill it, spill it.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
I'm not good at this.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You always open the door for me, don't you?
This is my first time opening one of these.
Are you okay?
I flew so high.I flew so high!
I love it.
Is this the team you want to be on?
That's interesting.
You know, you're the kind of creature that can't be bothered to drive a carpera.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, my God.
I'm good at this. I'm so good at this.
Hey, you're with me.
Because we have the same camera.
How did you not see that?
The lights came on.
The light hit me in the eye on the way out.
The electric light hit me in the eye on the way out.
I don't know which one is which.
It's normal.
Hmm?
There's something over there.
While the ever-vigilant Umezawa was wandering around the room...
Miraculously, he succeeded in replacing the pen.
And here he falls.
But here's the conversation...
What do you think this is a location shoot for?
What?
I think I put a hidden camera in the bulkhead.
Oh, my God. Now you're getting all heated up.
No, I just thought it was weird.
First of all, there were three different kinds of pens.
Where did I put the pens?
Why did you just pick that up?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know where my pen went.
Did you get it?
Ha-ha-ha.
Hey.
Always.
Oh, my God, aren't you good?
No, it's not that good.
Familiar with the main bone, the village
If you crack your knuckles, you'll complete mission 4.
Amazing!
Next, the three of us will aim to complete these three missions in cooperative play.
Cardboard Umezawa and Sato stand by in the room in advance.
Iwamoto enters the room with the target, Sakaguchi.
Iwamoto takes an ordinary pen and grabs Sakaguchi's pen, and the two of them start playing together.
Put this on.
Why did it ring?
Why didn't you put it on?
You're really good!
You're doing great!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
The three of us were having a great time.
Umezawa, the tall one, is gradually closing the distance
Ikekeke!
One more time!
Wow!
ohhhhhh!
oh oh oh!
Wow!
The advancing Umezawa approached Sakaguchi without being noticed at all by the team play of his peers.
His timing was perfect, too.His timing was perfect.
Sakaguchi showed a brilliant threat that blew up beautifully.
ohohohoh...
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I don't know why I cried.
I just cried.
You shouldn't have made me sit there.
You scared me.
Oh, my God.
How far did you get?
It's been fun.
Let's fill out the questionnaire.
Scary!
And then, without any explanation, Umezawa made his next move.
He'll make the next move.
Thank you, Mr. Umezawa.
That sounds great.
There's a sound.
It's delicious. It's so good.
It's good. It's good.
It's not good.
Delicious?
So, all the missions are completed.
What do you think this is?
It's a weird room.
The set-up was smooth.
Sakaguchi was a little crazy.
You'd better take him by surprise.
Be careful. It's not always a surprise.
I heard that Izukawa-san and others were scared of him.
I thought it was another surprise, but it turned out to be true.
Scary, scary, scary!
Shiori Kubo's first photo book will be released on July 11
Mobile 3rd selection for the Tokyo leg of the national tour has started!
Studio creation for the next unexpected trick
This is Tamami Sakaguchi.
If you don't subscribe to our channel, Tamami will win!
Watch by chance... bye!
ED.